{
    "subject": "resource/Casablanca_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/director",
    "object": "resource/Michael_Curtiz",
    "human_readable": "The director of Casablanca (film) is Michael Curtiz.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9491845965385437,
            "question": "Besides Casablanca, what other films has Michael Curtiz directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9410289525985718,
            "question": "Who directed the film Casablanca?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.906834602355957,
            "question": "Who is considered the director of Casablanca?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8886828422546387,
            "question": "Michael Curtiz was a director of which film genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8684497475624084,
            "question": "Name a movie directed by Michael Curtiz."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8264172673225403,
            "question": "What is the name of the director who made Casablanca?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8046560287475586,
            "question": "Is Michael Curtiz known for directing any famous films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8045281171798706,
            "question": "What film is associated with Michael Curtiz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7235485911369324,
            "question": "What film did Michael Curtiz direct?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3720199465751648,
            "question": "What year was Casablanca released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of Casablanca (film) is Michael Curtiz.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8647_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film did Michael Curtiz direct?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8647_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film is associated with Michael Curtiz?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8647_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Michael Curtiz known for directing any famous films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8647_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8647_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8647_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8647_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8647_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8647_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8647_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8647_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8647_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8647_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8647_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Casablanca, directed by Michael Curtiz\" and provide additional details about his role in the film. Therefore, the statement \"The director of Casablanca (film) is Michael Curtiz\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}